var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "يَأْتِي",
        "answer": "to come",
        "pcklId": "248",
        "tlit": "yatī",
        "frequency": "549",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأُخْرَىٰ",
        "answer": "And another",
        "pcklId": "218",
        "tlit": "wa-ukh'rā",
        "frequency": "250",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "229",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَإِذْ",
        "answer": "And when",
        "pcklId": "230",
        "tlit": "wa-idh",
        "frequency": "239",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُؤْذُونَنِي",
        "answer": "do you hurt me",
        "pcklId": "14",
        "tlit": "tu'dhūnanī",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضِ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "428",
        "tlit": "l-arḍi",
        "frequency": "461",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِسْرَائِيلَ",
        "answer": "(of) Israel",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "is'rāīla",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِسْرَائِيلَ",
        "answer": "(of) Israel",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "is'rāīla",
        "frequency": "43",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(you) who",
        "pcklId": "1337",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1338",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِي",
        "answer": "(is) the One Who",
        "pcklId": "1339",
        "tlit": "alladhī",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(you) who",
        "pcklId": "1340",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "who",
        "pcklId": "1341",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "those who",
        "pcklId": "1342",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَلِيمٍ",
        "answer": "painful",
        "pcklId": "68",
        "tlit": "alīmin",
        "frequency": "75",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2687",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2688",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهَ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2689",
        "tlit": "l-laha",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2690",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهُ",
        "answer": "(by) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2691",
        "tlit": "l-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "2692",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2693",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2694",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "And Allah",
        "pcklId": "2695",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2696",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَاللَّهُ",
        "answer": "but Allah",
        "pcklId": "2697",
        "tlit": "wal-lahu",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِاللَّهِ",
        "answer": "in Allah",
        "pcklId": "2698",
        "tlit": "bil-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2699",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2700",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2701",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "Allah",
        "pcklId": "2702",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "2703",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكُمْ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "683",
        "tlit": "ilaykum",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَيْكُمْ",
        "answer": "to you",
        "pcklId": "684",
        "tlit": "ilaykum",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "to",
        "pcklId": "685",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "إِلَى",
        "answer": "for",
        "pcklId": "686",
        "tlit": "ilā",
        "frequency": "742",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "517",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "518",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُؤْمِنُونَ",
        "answer": "Believe",
        "pcklId": "519",
        "tlit": "tu'minūna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believe",
        "pcklId": "520",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَآمَنَتْ",
        "answer": "Then believed",
        "pcklId": "521",
        "tlit": "faāmanat",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "آمَنُوا",
        "answer": "believed",
        "pcklId": "522",
        "tlit": "āmanū",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُؤْمِنِينَ",
        "answer": "(to) the believers",
        "pcklId": "834",
        "tlit": "l-mu'minīna",
        "frequency": "879",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَيَّدْنَا",
        "answer": "So We supported",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "fa-ayyadnā",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَبَشِّرِ",
        "answer": "and give glad tidings",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "wabashiri",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمُبَشِّرًا",
        "answer": "and bringing glad tidings",
        "pcklId": "121",
        "tlit": "wamubashiran",
        "frequency": "123",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَعْدِي",
        "answer": "after me",
        "pcklId": "134",
        "tlit": "baʿdī",
        "frequency": "235",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "ابْنُ",
        "answer": "son",
        "pcklId": "72",
        "tlit": "ub'nu",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "ابْنُ",
        "answer": "son",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "ub'nu",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا بَنِي",
        "answer": "O Children",
        "pcklId": "169",
        "tlit": "yābanī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَنِي",
        "answer": "Children",
        "pcklId": "170",
        "tlit": "banī",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "بُنْيَانٌ",
        "answer": "(were) a structure",
        "pcklId": "182",
        "tlit": "bun'yānun",
        "frequency": "184",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "بَيْنَ",
        "answer": "(was) between",
        "pcklId": "296",
        "tlit": "bayna",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْبَيِّنَاتِ",
        "answer": "with clear proofs",
        "pcklId": "376",
        "tlit": "bil-bayināti",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُبِينٌ",
        "answer": "clear",
        "pcklId": "515",
        "tlit": "mubīnun",
        "frequency": "523",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "تِجَارَةٍ",
        "answer": "a transaction",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "tijāratin",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَحْتِهَا",
        "answer": "underneath it",
        "pcklId": "42",
        "tlit": "taḥtihā",
        "frequency": "51",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُتِمُّ",
        "answer": "will perfect",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "mutimmu",
        "frequency": "22",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَجْرِي",
        "answer": "flow",
        "pcklId": "51",
        "tlit": "tajrī",
        "frequency": "64",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَنَّاتٍ",
        "answer": "(in) Gardens",
        "pcklId": "114",
        "tlit": "jannātin",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَنَّاتِ",
        "answer": "Gardens",
        "pcklId": "115",
        "tlit": "jannāti",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَتُجَاهِدُونَ",
        "answer": "and strive",
        "pcklId": "25",
        "tlit": "watujāhidūna",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "جَاءَهُمْ",
        "answer": "he came to them",
        "pcklId": "264",
        "tlit": "jāahum",
        "frequency": "278",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُحِبُّ",
        "answer": "loves",
        "pcklId": "60",
        "tlit": "yuḥibbu",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُحِبُّونَهَا",
        "answer": "that you love ",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "tuḥibbūnahā",
        "frequency": "95",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَقِّ",
        "answer": "(of) the truth",
        "pcklId": "272",
        "tlit": "l-ḥaqi",
        "frequency": "287",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَكِيمُ",
        "answer": "the All-Wise",
        "pcklId": "184",
        "tlit": "l-ḥakīmu",
        "frequency": "210",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلْحَوَارِيِّينَ",
        "answer": "to the disciples",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "lil'ḥawāriyyīna",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَوَارِيُّونَ",
        "answer": "the disciples",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "l-ḥawāriyūna",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) better",
        "pcklId": "137",
        "tlit": "khayrun",
        "frequency": "196",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَيُدْخِلْكُمْ",
        "answer": "and admit you",
        "pcklId": "111",
        "tlit": "wayud'khil'kum",
        "frequency": "126",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُدْعَىٰ",
        "answer": "is invited",
        "pcklId": "157",
        "tlit": "yud'ʿā",
        "frequency": "212",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَدُلُّكُمْ",
        "answer": "I guide you",
        "pcklId": "6",
        "tlit": "adullukum",
        "frequency": "8",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَدِينِ",
        "answer": "and (the) religion",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "wadīni",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدِّينِ",
        "answer": "the religion",
        "pcklId": "79",
        "tlit": "l-dīni",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "ذُنُوبَكُمْ",
        "answer": "your sins",
        "pcklId": "32",
        "tlit": "dhunūbakum",
        "frequency": "39",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَرْسَلَ",
        "answer": "sent",
        "pcklId": "122",
        "tlit": "arsala",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولُ",
        "answer": "(the) Messenger",
        "pcklId": "444",
        "tlit": "rasūlu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولُ",
        "answer": "(the) Messenger",
        "pcklId": "445",
        "tlit": "rasūlu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِرَسُولٍ",
        "answer": "(of) a Messenger",
        "pcklId": "446",
        "tlit": "birasūlin",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَسُولَهُ",
        "answer": "His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "447",
        "tlit": "rasūlahu",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَرَسُولِهِ",
        "answer": "and His Messenger",
        "pcklId": "448",
        "tlit": "warasūlihi",
        "frequency": "513",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَرْصُوصٌ",
        "answer": "joined firmly",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "marṣūṣun",
        "frequency": "1",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُرِيدُونَ",
        "answer": "They intend",
        "pcklId": "139",
        "tlit": "yurīdūna",
        "frequency": "148",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "زَاغُوا",
        "answer": "they deviated",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "zāghū",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَزَاغَ",
        "answer": "(was caused to) deviate",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "azāgha",
        "frequency": "9",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبَّحَ",
        "answer": "Glorifies",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "tlit": "sabbaḥa",
        "frequency": "92",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلِهِ",
        "answer": "His Way",
        "pcklId": "166",
        "tlit": "sabīlihi",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "سَبِيلِ",
        "answer": "(the) way",
        "pcklId": "167",
        "tlit": "sabīli",
        "frequency": "176",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "سِحْرٌ",
        "answer": "(is) a magic",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "siḥ'run",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَمَسَاكِنَ",
        "answer": "and dwellings",
        "pcklId": "41",
        "tlit": "wamasākina",
        "frequency": "69",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِسْلَامِ",
        "answer": "Islam",
        "pcklId": "94",
        "tlit": "l-is'lāmi",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "اسْمُهُ",
        "answer": "whose name (will be)",
        "pcklId": "40",
        "tlit": "us'muhu",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "السَّمَاوَاتِ",
        "answer": "the heavens",
        "pcklId": "327",
        "tlit": "l-samāwāti",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُشْرِكُونَ",
        "answer": "the polytheists",
        "pcklId": "158",
        "tlit": "l-mush'rikūna",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "فَأَصْبَحُوا",
        "answer": "and they became",
        "pcklId": "26",
        "tlit": "fa-aṣbaḥū",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "مُصَدِّقًا",
        "answer": "confirming",
        "pcklId": "145",
        "tlit": "muṣaddiqan",
        "frequency": "155",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "صَفًّا",
        "answer": "(in) a row",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "ṣaffan",
        "frequency": "14",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيُطْفِئُوا",
        "answer": "to put out",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "liyuṭ'fiū",
        "frequency": "3",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَائِفَةٌ",
        "answer": "a group",
        "pcklId": "30",
        "tlit": "ṭāifatun",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَائِفَةٌ",
        "answer": "a group",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "ṭāifatun",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "طَيِّبَةً",
        "answer": "pleasant",
        "pcklId": "48",
        "tlit": "ṭayyibatan",
        "frequency": "50",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَظْلَمُ",
        "answer": "(is) more wrong",
        "pcklId": "126",
        "tlit": "aẓlamu",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "الظَّالِمِينَ",
        "answer": "[the] wrongdoers",
        "pcklId": "305",
        "tlit": "l-ẓālimīna",
        "frequency": "315",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيُظْهِرَهُ",
        "answer": "to make it prevail",
        "pcklId": "21",
        "tlit": "liyuẓ'hirahu",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "ظَاهِرِينَ",
        "answer": "dominant",
        "pcklId": "56",
        "tlit": "ẓāhirīna",
        "frequency": "59",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَدُوِّهِمْ",
        "answer": "their enemy",
        "pcklId": "74",
        "tlit": "ʿaduwwihim",
        "frequency": "106",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "عَذَابٍ",
        "answer": "a punishment",
        "pcklId": "338",
        "tlit": "ʿadhābin",
        "frequency": "373",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَزِيزُ",
        "answer": "(is) the All-Mighty",
        "pcklId": "66",
        "tlit": "l-ʿazīzu",
        "frequency": "119",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَظِيمُ",
        "answer": "the great",
        "pcklId": "103",
        "tlit": "l-ʿaẓīmu",
        "frequency": "128",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "you know",
        "pcklId": "348",
        "tlit": "taʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَعْلَمُونَ",
        "answer": "know",
        "pcklId": "349",
        "tlit": "taʿlamūna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "عِنْدَ",
        "answer": "with",
        "pcklId": "148",
        "tlit": "ʿinda",
        "frequency": "201",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَغْفِرْ",
        "answer": "He will forgive",
        "pcklId": "57",
        "tlit": "yaghfir",
        "frequency": "234",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَفَتْحٌ",
        "answer": "and a victory",
        "pcklId": "31",
        "tlit": "wafatḥun",
        "frequency": "38",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "افْتَرَىٰ",
        "answer": "invents",
        "pcklId": "50",
        "tlit": "if'tarā",
        "frequency": "60",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَاسِقِينَ",
        "answer": "the defiantly disobedient",
        "pcklId": "52",
        "tlit": "l-fāsiqīna",
        "frequency": "54",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَفْعَلُونَ",
        "answer": "you do",
        "pcklId": "77",
        "tlit": "tafʿalūna",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَفْعَلُونَ",
        "answer": "you do",
        "pcklId": "78",
        "tlit": "tafʿalūna",
        "frequency": "108",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْفَوْزُ",
        "answer": "(is) the success",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "l-fawzu",
        "frequency": "29",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَفْوَاهِهِمْ",
        "answer": "with their mouths",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "tlit": "bi-afwāhihim",
        "frequency": "13",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "يُقَاتِلُونَ",
        "answer": "fight",
        "pcklId": "138",
        "tlit": "yuqātilūna",
        "frequency": "170",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَرِيبٌ",
        "answer": "near",
        "pcklId": "73",
        "tlit": "qarībun",
        "frequency": "96",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "قُلُوبَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their hearts",
        "pcklId": "150",
        "tlit": "qulūbahum",
        "frequency": "168",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقُولُونَ",
        "answer": "(do) you say",
        "pcklId": "1535",
        "tlit": "taqūlūna",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "تَقُولُوا",
        "answer": "you say",
        "pcklId": "1536",
        "tlit": "taqūlū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "said",
        "pcklId": "1537",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "said",
        "pcklId": "1538",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالُوا",
        "answer": "they said",
        "pcklId": "1539",
        "tlit": "qālū",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "said",
        "pcklId": "1540",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "قَالَ",
        "answer": "Said",
        "pcklId": "1541",
        "tlit": "qāla",
        "frequency": "1722",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِقَوْمِهِ",
        "answer": "to his people",
        "pcklId": "475",
        "tlit": "liqawmihi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَا قَوْمِ",
        "answer": "O my people",
        "pcklId": "476",
        "tlit": "yāqawmi",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمَ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "477",
        "tlit": "l-qawma",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْقَوْمَ",
        "answer": "the people",
        "pcklId": "478",
        "tlit": "l-qawma",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَبُرَ",
        "answer": "Great is",
        "pcklId": "7",
        "tlit": "kabura",
        "frequency": "161",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَذِبَ",
        "answer": "the lie",
        "pcklId": "223",
        "tlit": "l-kadhiba",
        "frequency": "282",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَرِهَ",
        "answer": "dislike",
        "pcklId": "15",
        "tlit": "kariha",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "كَرِهَ",
        "answer": "dislike (it)",
        "pcklId": "16",
        "tlit": "kariha",
        "frequency": "41",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَكَفَرَتْ",
        "answer": "and disbelieved",
        "pcklId": "269",
        "tlit": "wakafarat",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْكَافِرُونَ",
        "answer": "the disbelievers",
        "pcklId": "503",
        "tlit": "l-kāfirūna",
        "frequency": "525",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُلِّهِ",
        "answer": "all of them",
        "pcklId": "336",
        "tlit": "kullihi",
        "frequency": "377",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُنْتُمْ",
        "answer": "you",
        "pcklId": "1275",
        "tlit": "kuntum",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "كُونُوا",
        "answer": "Be",
        "pcklId": "1276",
        "tlit": "kūnū",
        "frequency": "1390",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَقْتًا",
        "answer": "hatred",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "maqtan",
        "frequency": "6",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِأَمْوَالِكُمْ",
        "answer": "with your wealth",
        "pcklId": "70",
        "tlit": "bi-amwālikum",
        "frequency": "86",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "تُنْجِيكُمْ",
        "answer": "(that) will save you",
        "pcklId": "61",
        "tlit": "tunjīkum",
        "frequency": "84",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "10"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَصْرٌ",
        "answer": "a help",
        "pcklId": "89",
        "tlit": "naṣrun",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "13"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْصَارَ",
        "answer": "helpers",
        "pcklId": "136",
        "tlit": "anṣāra",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْصَارِي",
        "answer": "(are) my helpers",
        "pcklId": "137",
        "tlit": "anṣārī",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْصَارُ",
        "answer": "(are) the helpers",
        "pcklId": "138",
        "tlit": "anṣāru",
        "frequency": "158",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "14"
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَنْفُسِكُمْ",
        "answer": "and your lives",
        "pcklId": "277",
        "tlit": "wa-anfusikum",
        "frequency": "298",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "11"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَنْهَارُ",
        "answer": "the rivers",
        "pcklId": "106",
        "tlit": "l-anhāru",
        "frequency": "113",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "12"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُورَ",
        "answer": "(the) light",
        "pcklId": "181",
        "tlit": "nūra",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "نُورِهِ",
        "answer": "His Light",
        "pcklId": "182",
        "tlit": "nūrihi",
        "frequency": "194",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "8"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْدِي",
        "answer": "guide",
        "pcklId": "131",
        "tlit": "yahdī",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَهْدِي",
        "answer": "guide",
        "pcklId": "132",
        "tlit": "yahdī",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِالْهُدَىٰ",
        "answer": "with guidance",
        "pcklId": "279",
        "tlit": "bil-hudā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "9"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَدَيَّ",
        "answer": "my hands",
        "pcklId": "112",
        "tlit": "yadayya",
        "frequency": "120",
        "surah": "61",
        "ayah": "6"
    }
]; 
export default words;